<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bike on Sunny Sewing</title>
    <link>https://sunny-sewing.com/tags/bike/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bike on Sunny Sewing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunny-sewing.com/tags/bike/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2) The cycle of problems and solutions</title>
      <link>https://sunny-sewing.com/2-the-cycle-of-problems-and-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sunny-sewing.com/2-the-cycle-of-problems-and-solutions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To do any sewing, you&amp;rsquo;re certainly going to need a table. As tables are generally not so portable, some thought is required on this one&amp;hellip;
After a while I came up with the idea to mount my sewing machine on the back of my bike. Here you have the advantage that the bike takes the load of the machine and other gubbins while the whole setup is easily transportable - the perfect solution, at least in theory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second issue is one of power - the sewing machine has to run off of something, be it electricity or human power. I decided to opt for the latter after I found a nice treadle powered sewing machine on ebay.
All that is left to do is attach it to the bicycle, which could look something like this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img id=&#34;col&#34; src=&#34;https://sunny-sewing.com/bike1.jpg&#34;  width=45% /&gt;&lt;img id=&#34;col&#34; src=&#34;https://sunny-sewing.com/bike2.jpg&#34;  width=45% /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I were more thoughtful and less enthusiastic I would have realised that such a contraption is &lt;strong&gt;monstrously&lt;/strong&gt; heavy.
If I were not a total moron, I would&amp;rsquo;ve been able to figure out that with the machine over the back wheel like so, the bike would become very difficult to ride and manoeuvre. And all that is without the treadle mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nevermind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still think that the whole bike mounted concept is fine; now the main problem is finding a sewing machine that isn&amp;rsquo;t preposterous heavy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Post</title>
      <link>https://sunny-sewing.com/the-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sunny-sewing.com/the-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When someone tells you they sew, you probably imagine that they spend hours hunched over a table in a corner that looks something like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img class=&#34;special-img-class&#34; src=&#34;https://sunny-sewing.com/machine_c.jpg&#34;  width=60% /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A dark corner crammed with scissors, rulers, scraps of fabric and other mysterious objects that you don&amp;rsquo;t even know the names of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine that the weather outside is nice but you are feeling creative. You have to choose between going outside and enjoying the sun, or sitting in the dark corner with the sewing machine.
I think that is a shame and want to change that! Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great if you could go outside, to the park or even the beach, take your fabrics and make something there and then? Of course it would be great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is however easier said than done. Your sewing machine, like mine, could probably have a successful second life as a prop in strongman events. Then comes all the other stuff you need like electricity, pins, needles, various old biscuit tins full of junk and more pins to replace the ones that you will lose.
If you want to sew outside, the prospects seem so bleak that you&amp;rsquo;d be better advised to stop reading this and find a donkey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to make sewing in the fresh air possible and this site will chronicle my ideas in this journey and what comes out at the end of it. I am excited to see where it leads us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
